{
    "id": "b77d8fd8d5c645f28ab135b8ccc25400",
    "title": "Question Tags Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "You can sing well, ……………………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can you",
                "can't you",
                "don't you"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She came yesterday, ……………………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hadn't she",
                "did she",
                "didn't she"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Shut the door, .....................?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will you",
                "won't you",
                "can't you",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "Let’s have some tea, ……………………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will we",
                "shall we",
                "should we"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She broke the glass, ……………………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did she",
                "didn't she",
                "hadn't she"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He will come, ……………………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will he",
                "won't he",
                "can't he"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He doesn’t have many friends, ……………………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "does he",
                "doesn't he",
                "do he"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He seldom watches films, ……………………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "does he",
                "doesn't he",
                "has he"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I am free now, ……………………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "amn't I",
                "aren't I",
                "am I"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He is a doctor, ……………………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "isn't he",
                "is he",
                "doesn't he"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She is coming with us, ……………………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is she",
                "isn't she",
                "hasn't she"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We won’t tolerate this, ………………… ..?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will we",
                "won't we",
                "would we"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I didn’t expect this, …………………… .?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did I",
                "didn't I",
                "don't I"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He waited for an hour, …………………… ..?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did he",
                "didn't he",
                "don't he"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}